<stl:stl xmlns:stl="http://developer.opentext.com/schemas/storyteller/layout" version="0.1">
  <stl:data>
	<stl:template>
	  <data>
		<message priority='L'>
		  Forth Run [1]PT_BILL_3.5_003 CorpCommunications screen for bill messages. The expectation to turn around
		  LC scripts within a day is fast approaching. Please read this email from Stephan. This report tracks the # of
		  days scripts are with us and have 0 high or critical defects # meaning the scripts steps should be continued.
		  I#m scheduling a meeting for us tomorrow and will add this to the agenda. As of right now, if you#re going
		  on vacation and have an open script, please reassign it to another team member. Also, when you finish your
		  script and send it to the next time, it is critical that you change the assigned to team or else it will show as still
		  with Billing. Here#s an example of a script that shows assigned to Billing, but it#s really with Maria Brothers in
		  SO.
		</message>
		<message priority='M'>
		  Fith run, Low priority marketing Message. Repeat Whole Scenario from step 20 to 120, for Create a statement
		  where there are more messages than available space on statement. By adding Create a one-time message
		  for a customer (U of M). Create a regulatory, Confirm that messages prioritize accordingly and lowest priority
		  message per business rules fall off the bottom of the statement and do not truncate mid-message.
		</message>
		<message priority='L'>
		  Third run PT_BILL_3.5_003 CorpCommunications screen for bill messages Repeat Whole Scenario from step
		  20 to 120, by adding Create a recurring message with an expiration date. Generate the statement associated to
		  the target market. Invoice next month after the message expiration date lapses.Expected: Message is created
		  successfully for customer on next bill. Follow statement next month where the validity date has lapsed does not
		  contain the message.
		</message>
		<message priority='H'>
		  Sixth Run [1]PT_BILL_3.5_003 CorpCommunications screen for bill messages Posting date
		</message>
		<message priority='L'>
		  DTE Energy reports the payment histories of all customers to the major credit reporting agencies. Paying your
		  bill in full and on time, or entering into a payment agreement can help you avoid having unfavorable payment
		  information reported to a credit reporting agency.
		</message>
	  </data>
	</stl:template>
	<stl:transformation>
	  <tdt:transformation xmlns:tdt="http://developer.opentext.com/schemas/storyteller/transformation/tdt" version="1.0" />
	</stl:transformation>
  </stl:data>
  <stl:style>
	.cell {
	  padding:2 2 2 2; 
	  border:solid black;
	}
	.high-priority {
	  text-align:left; 
      font-family:Arial; 
      font-size:10; 
      color:red;
    }
	.low-priority {
	  text-align:left; 
      font-family:Arial; 
      font-size:10; 
      color:black;
    }
  </stl:style>
  <stl:document>
	<stl:story name="Shared">
	  <stl:p>
		<stl:table>
		  <stl:story>
			<stl:repeater xpath="/data/message[@priority='H']">
			  <stl:row>
				<stl:cell w="490" class="cell">
				  <stl:p class="high-priority"><stl:field xpath="normalize-space(.)"/></stl:p>
				</stl:cell>
			  </stl:row>
			</stl:repeater>
			<stl:repeater xpath="/data/message[@priority='M']">
			  <stl:row>
				<stl:cell w="490" class="cell">
				  <stl:p class="high-priority"><stl:field xpath="normalize-space(.)"/></stl:p>
				</stl:cell>
			  </stl:row>
			</stl:repeater>
			<stl:repeater xpath="/data/message[@priority='L']">
			  <stl:row>
				<stl:cell w="490" class="cell">
				  <stl:script when="after" language="js">
					var layout = require('layout');
					var item = layout.item();
					console.log( item );
					item.Visibility = 'Invisible';
				  </stl:script>
				  <stl:p class="low-priority">
					<stl:field xpath="normalize-space(.)"/>
				  </stl:p>
				</stl:cell>
			  </stl:row>
			</stl:repeater>
		  </stl:story>
		</stl:table>
	  </stl:p>
	</stl:story>
	<stl:page w="540" h="500">
	  <stl:text x="20" y="20" w="500" h="480" story="Shared"/>
	</stl:page>
	<stl:page w="540" h="500">
	  <stl:text x="20" y="20" w="500" h="60" story="Shared"/>
	</stl:page>
  </stl:document>
</stl:stl>
